* [English (US)](https://whizz.com/en-us/privacy-policy/ "English (US)")

Menu

    * [English (US)](https://whizz.com/en-us/privacy-policy/ "English (US)")

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective Date: 1 January, 2021

### Your privacy is our priority

Since 25th May, 2018, Whizz Education’s **Data Protection Policy** has been in compliance with the EU Regulation 2016/679 General Data Protection Regulation (“EU GDPR”). With effect from 1st January, 2021, our policy will be in compliance with the UK GDPR and the amended Data Protection Act 2018.

**Privacy Statements** explain how we use, manage and protect your Personal Data and your rights relating to it. There are individual Privacy Statements for (1) our Maths-Whizz students whether at home or in school (2) teachers in schools using Maths-Whizz and (3) home subscribers to Maths-Whizz. We are especially conscious of the need to protect information concerning children using Maths-Whizz. We have done our best to write our Privacy Statement for them in language they will be able to understand.

Our **Data Protection Supplementary Statement for Schools** covers our policy and the obligations which we and our school customers undertake with respect to Personal Data shared between us. With effect from 1st January, 2021, we will be agreeing Standard Contractual Clauses with our school customers in the European Economic Area with respect to their data transfers from the EEA to the UK.

Please click below to view all our Data Protection and Privacy Statements and/or to access a Subject Access Request Form:

If you have questions regarding our Data Protection Policy or any other matter related to data protection and privacy, please don’t hesitate to contact us at [dpo@whizz.com](mailto:dpo@whizz.com). Customers in the European Economic Area should contact our EU Data Representative, Ms Asem Koshkarbayeva at 10, Avenue du Maréchal Foch, 06000, Nice, email: [asem.koshkarbayeva@whizz.com](mailto:asem.koshkarbayeva@whizz.com).

You may also want to view our Subscription Agreements/Access Agreements in respect of Maths-Whizz Tutoring Plus for Parents, Maths-Whizz Tutoring Plus for Schools and Maths-Whizz Teachers’ Resource which can be found on our [Subscription Agreements](https://www.whizz.com/subscription-agreements-2/) page.

* * *

For Parents
-----------

For Schools
-----------

Contact Us
----------

* +44 (0) 203 328 6564

© 2024 Whizz Education Limited | One Kingdom Street, Paddington Central London, W2 6BD, United Kingdom.

[Eco](https://whizz.com/eco/) | [Legal](https://whizz.com/legal/) | [Cookies & Privacy Policy](https://whizz.com/privacy-policy/) | [Web Design](https://red-giraffe.com/) by [Red Giraffe](https://red-giraffe.com/seo/)
